So I posted the video of the Amazon delivery woman being accosted and attacked.
Excuse me, don't touch me.
No, we've had thieves here and you're a thief.
But in true black people fashion, I don't know if it's because we always have to,
but we can only take things seriously, but so much.
And then we got to throw in the comedy.
Here are some of the responses.
I'd have to lose my job that day.
Attacking?
Ma'am, where?
Where?
Granny would have got a two-piece and a biscuit.
See, God don't bless me with these types of situations,
because Karen would have got drop kicked.
Couldn't be me.
Amazon needs to give her hazard pay.
Y'all have been walking around here wearing granny on t-shirts,
because it wouldn't have been me that day.
On addition, y'all have had to get on that GoFundMe and post my bail
and call attorney Bancrump, because the way my rage is set up.
Again, shout out to this sister.
I'm sorry that you had to experience that.
This is what it is to be black, not just in America, but in the world.
You hear about sisters on trips to Italy and how they're getting followed around and harassed
and they want to leave because this is terrible in the country.
When you see how folks in China was treating the black students during COVID,
when you see how in Ukraine, when war broke out,
they wasn't letting black folks on the train to make it out the country.
It's not just here and we have to make it our business to destroy it on the planet.